所以Insta360新推出了Ace Pro
So Insta360 has a new Ace Pro
Ace Pro 2
the Ace Pro 2
而且前面依然有徕卡的标志 显示了合作开发的特色
and they've still got that Leica badge on the front, co-engineered.
这当然是他们的8K AI运动相机 配有可翻转的显示屏
This, of course, is their 8K AI-powered action camera with a flippy display
这样你就能看到自己了
so you can see yourself.
看起来更加坚固了
It looks more rugged than ever.
他们给了我一张小卡片 上面写着1比1.3
They gave me this little slip, say 1 over 1.3.
这是一颗搭载徕卡镜头的8K传感器
The size of the 8K sensor with a Leica lens on it.
支持8K 30帧的视频和5000万像素照片
8K 30 frames per second video, 50 megapixel photos,
还配备了双人工智能芯片 以提升图像质量
and a dual AI chip for superior image quality.
他们声称改善了低光拍摄性能
They claim to have enhanced the low light performance.
他们声称改善了防风设计 以确保录音清晰
They claim to have enhanced the wind guard for clear audio when recording.
我们还可以拍摄4K 60帧
We can also shoot 4K 60 frames
我觉得对大多数人来说
which I think is actually going to be more useful for more people
这比8K画面更实用
than the 8K footage.
坚固耐用 防水性能可达39英尺 支持157度广角拍摄
Rugged and waterproof to 39 feet, 157 degree wide angle capture.
当然 我们还提供AI编辑
Of course, we've also got our AI editing
这个功能也集成在应用程序中
which is built into the app as well.
所以Insta360让我对比
So Insta360 actually asked me to show the footage next to
Ace Pro 2和GoPro 13 Black的画面
the footage from the GoPro 13 Black.
这说明他们对自己产品非常有信心
That's how confident they are in their product.
接下来你会看到一些样品
So you're going to see some samples
你可以自己判断
and you can decide for yourself
当你比较图像质量时
when you see the image quality comparatively
在几种不同的场景中
in a couple of different scenarios.
它似乎附带了双电池包
It looks like it comes with a dual battery bundle
这总是很棒的
which is always kind of nice.
我想你可以选择不同的套件来订购它
I presume you can order this in a couple of different kits
但两个电池总会更好
but two batteries is better than one.
他们也有很好的防抖功能
They've also got very nice smoothing
还有高动态范围（HDR）技术 让画面更加清晰、易于观看
and HDR to keep everything nice and watchable.
在这里 你可以看到它们称之为'流畅稳定'
Here you can see they call it flow state stabilized.
而这个地平线锁定功能 简直就像魔法一样
And that horizon lock is basically like magic.
这看起来确实挺不一样的
This does look different.
麦克风的网罩换了个样子
The microphone grill has changed.
贴纸1
Sticker one.
贴纸2
Sticker two.
整个设备看起来非常耐用 几乎就像单反相机
The whole thing feels quite rugged, almost like a SLR style camera.
如果你想让显示屏保持
The display locks into place if you wanna
在常规格式 它会自动锁定
keep it locked out in its regular format
当然 它也能轻松卡入到位
but then obviously it clicks into place
在前置拍摄时
in the front facing scenario as well.
这样你就可以轻松伸出手 看到自己的样子
So you can easily hold this out, see yourself.
即使你使用了一根自拍杆
And even if you have it on some sort of an extension selfie stick
你依然能看到自己
you can still see yourself on there.
徕卡126胜过13
Leica 126 over 13.
它还有一个副屏和一个大的录制按钮
You've also got this secondary front display and a large record button.
电源开关在另一边
Power switch over on the other side.
把这个翻下来
Flip this back down.
电池
Battery.
放在这里
Fits into this location here.
盖子会紧密封闭
And the lid kind of seals into place
防止电池进水和进尘土
in order to seal off the battery from moisture and dust.
此外 这里还有一个USB-C和microSD的专用插口
And then we have a separate door for our USB-C as well as our microSD.
包装里还有这些内容
Also in the package
一堆文件
a tremendous amount of paperwork
这是相机的经典现象之一
which is kind of a classic thing with cameras.
以前的相机一般会有比较厚的手册
Thicker booklets have historically come with cameras.
还有一些Insta360的贴纸
And actually, some Insta360 stickers as well.
可以想象是那些手册
Think booklets.
令人惊叹
bold.
我们配备了一根更加耐用的USB-C数据线和一些扎带
We have our USB-C cable with some cable ties, a little more robust.
另外 这里还有一个磁性连接
And remember, we have this magnetic connection,
至少在视频的前半部分是磁性的
which at least the first portion of the clip is magnetic.
这样可以帮助你自动对齐
So it kind of lines it up for you
然后你只需要轻轻一按就可以了
and then you just click it in.
所以这既是磁性的 又有机械连接的特性
So it's both magnetic and mechanical.
要拆卸的时候
And then in order to release it
你需要两边抓住 然后用力拔出来
you have to grab from both sides and pull it out.
这样处理起来会更加爽快
It just makes it a little bit more satisfying
比起单一的方法 使用起来更简单一些
and a little bit easier than having just one
而不是单纯依赖机械接点
or the other just having a mechanical connection point instead
我们通过这种方式确保连接顺畅
here we make sure things are lined up
这样一连就能快速连接上了
and then we're in it's pretty quick
当然 你现在可以把它连接到不同的配件上
and of course you can now attach this to a variety of accessories
这款电池无需外部盒子
without the need for any kind of like external case
这是我们的第二块电池
here is our second battery
这也是套餐中的一部分
since it's part of the bundle
这个是防风罩
so this one is the wind guard
这是麦克风盖 入水时请使用它
and this is the mic cap if you're going to head into water you use this cap
如果你要在风中拍摄的话 哦
And if you're going to be filming in the wind, oh
我居然没注意到！
I didn't even notice.
这个夹子里面是泡沫
So there's foam on the inside of this clip.
这就是它的原理
So that's how that's working.
这不仅仅是个有孔的格栅
So it's not just a perforated grill.
后面还有泡沫
There's foam behind there.
如果你之前看过的话
And if you've seen in the past
说到降低风噪音
when it comes to reducing wind noise
你通常会用泡沫状的材料
you always have sort of like a foam
或者是一个夹在外面的毛绒防风罩
or a dead cat that you would clip onto the outside.
不过那看起来有点难看
But that's a little bit ugly.
这显然是个更简洁的解决方案
This is definitely a cleaner solution
而且它不会轻易掉下来
and it's not going to fall off
因为它是固定网罩的一部分
because it's part of the rigid grill.
哦 我们快速比较一下这个机身
Oh, let's do a quick comparison just of the body
和前一代的不同
comparative to the previous generation.
这就是Ace Pro
So this was the Ace Pro
现在我们来看看 Ace Pro 2
and now we have the Ace Pro 2.
显然 最引人注目的就是这个新的麦克风位置
Definitely the standout aspect is this new microphone location
和配件了
and accessory.
机身形态没有太大变化
It doesn't really change the form factor all that much
因为镜头本身就有些凸出
because the lens is protruding anyways.
我觉得把这个屏幕加进来是个不错的设计
So integrating that screen I think is a nice thing.
录制按钮现在完全是圆形的
The record button is now completely circular
不再是之前方形按钮内的红圈了
instead of just being a red circle inside of a square button.
显示屏的实际显示区域似乎大了一些
display looks a little bit larger not the frame of it
而且 新的电池盖表现得更好 真是超赞
but the actual active display area the new battery door is way better holy
这开起来真不太让人满意
so this is not very satisfying to open
关闭Ace Pro的电池盖
and close this the battery door on the ace pro
与新电池盖相比 感觉更好
at least comparatively the new battery door
发出轻微的咔嗒声
it just there's a little click
而且释放手感更加令人放心
and the release is much more confidence inspiring you hear
那个咔嗒声
that little click
是啊 他们的确改进了很多
yeah they really improved it
Mo现在把Ace 2 Pro拿出来了
so mo has now taken the ace 2 pro out
并进行了充分测试
and put it through its paces
我打算对比最新的GoPro拍的录像
and i am going to examine the footage
看看能不能找出区别
comparative to the latest gopro see if i can spot the differences
我们还聊聊
and also just talk about some of the improvements
他们对Ace Pro 2进行的一些改进
they've made in the ace pro 2
因为有很多升级 像新的1/1.3传感器
because there are a number of upgrades including the new 1 over 1.3 sensor
这是8K 30帧的画面 看看这美丽的秋天色彩
this is the 8k 30 footage look at the beautiful autumn colors
细节非常丰富
plenty of detail here
运动相机的稳定性很不错
from an action camera stabilization as well
颜色非常鲜艳
We have extremely vibrant, I mean
显然 秋天的树叶确实为画面增添了许多色彩
obviously the fall leaves help with that,
颜色饱和且细节丰富
but very vibrant, saturated colors and tremendous detail.
这就是8K 30帧的画面
It's 8K 30.
我的显示器并不是8K 但
My display is not even 8K, but.
哦 你捕到了一只兔子！
Oh, you caught a rabbit.
兔子心里会想
The rabbit's like
你这台运动相机是干什么用的？
what are you doing with this action camera?
就像你正在树林里一样 兄弟
Like you're in the bush, man.
他现在觉得自己像是被追捕了
He thinks he's being hunted right now.
在8K画质下 最能展示出这些细节
in 8k most showcasing how
使用8K拍摄后 你可以在后期调整更多画面 效果更好
when you start with 8k you still got more you've got more reach in post
因为你可以放大到两倍
because you can go to 2x
而且效果仍然不错 完全可以使用
and it's still still good enough to use
对于运动相机来说 这点非常不错
which on an action camera is kind of nice
因为你希望广角 这样就不会错过精彩瞬间
because you want to be as wide as possible so you don't miss the action
不过在编辑的时候
but then when you're editing it
你可能想把人物拉得更近一些
you might want to bring people into a closer point
因为实在太宽了
because it's just so wide
而且很难看明白
and hard to tell what's going on
使用这款摄影机 能轻松进行2倍裁剪
but when you start with ak to begin with you can easily do a 2x crop
现在咱们看到的是4K 120 怎么会有这么多叶子飘落呢？
and here we have 4k 120 How do you have so many leaves falling?
你把那些叶子抛到空中了
You threw those up in the air.
嗯
Yeah.
你现在只是在做视频壁纸
You're just making wallpapers right now.
就像视频壁纸和屏保那样
Like video wallpapers, screen savers.
真美！
That's beautiful.
这就是他们所称的4K清晰变焦
So this is what they call 4K clarity zoom.
这不是后期合成的效果
And this is not in post.
只需在屏幕上双击 就能激活4K清晰变焦
This is a double tap on the display in order to engage the 4K clarity zoom.
4K 30 HDR 激活HDR
4K 30 HDR, active HDR.
在这种情况下
Yeah, so in this case
Mo在做的就是增强图像的对比度效果
what Mo's doing is he's trying to have a ton of contrast in the image.
所以太阳实际上在画面中 显然会呈现过曝的效果
So the sun is actually in the frame, obviously going to be blown out
并且前景较暗
and a darker foreground
以查看它如何处理其中的阴影
to see how it deals with the shadows in the foreground.
这正是Insta360的核心魅力所在
This is sort of what it's all about for Insta360.
在Ace Pro上也差不多 Ace Pro 2更为明显
It was similar on the Ace Pro, even more so on the Ace Pro 2
突出低光表现的优势
to highlight the highlight, the low light performance.
这当然是不可少的部分
This is, of course
就是新处理系统和显而易见的新传感器的作用
where the new processing system comes in and obviously the new sensor.
大家可以看到 哇 这真是
As you can see, Wow, that's
现在是什么时候啊？
this is what time of day is this?
这是夜晚的场景
This is night.
这是说 现在大概多晚了？
This is like, how late is this?
这是早上五点吗？真是太晚了！
This is five in the morning?
哇 真是不可思议！
Damn.
总之 你可以明显看到这里的区别
Anyway, you can sort of spot the difference here.
还有一个额外的好处是
And the other benefit that's happening is
因为系统能获取更多信息
because the system is getting more information
得益于低光环境下的表现
because of the low light performance
它能够提供更多数据给稳定器
it's able to feed more into the stabilizer
识别情况的能力
the ability to discern what's going on
这样你能获得更稳定的画面 减少抖动
but you also end up with a more stable image with less rattles.
我想说
I mean,
没错
yeah.
听着 兄弟
Look, man.
显然 右侧的画面很难看清楚
Obviously, hard to see what's going on in the frame on the right,
这是GoPro画面
the GoPro frame.
如果图像更清晰一些
If you have more detail in the image
这有助于提高画面的稳定性
it's going to aid in the stabilization.
就这样
That's it.
这就是我们现在看到的情况
That's kind of what we're witnessing here.
把手势控制打开
Turn on gesture control.
哦 真快啊
Oh, that's quick, actually.
现在我能看到它在录制
Now I can see the fact that it's recording
因为前面有个红灯
because I have a red light on the front
我可以停止录制了
and I can go ahead and Stop the recording.
这真的很清晰又迅速
That's just really crisp and fast.
开始录！
Start recording.
非常快速 而且很简单
Very quick, easy.
暂停录制！
Stop recording.
快拍一张！
Take a photo.
非常连贯
Very, very coherent.
感觉完全没有延迟或处理时间
Like there's no lag or processing time.
开始录！
Start recording.
标记这个片段
Mark that clip.
暂停录制！
Stop recording.
这就是与徕卡联合研发的新款Insta360 Ace Pro 2
So that's the new Insta360 Ace Pro 2, co-engineered with Leica
这款运动相机现在可以以30帧录制8K视频
8K on an action camera now at 30 frames.
还有很多其他实用的功能和特色
Also, a ton of other useful functions and features.
支持4K120和纯视频4K60
4K 120, pure video 4K 60
我自己可能会经常使用这个
which I would probably shoot in a lot myself.
风挡设计更优
The better design on the windscreen,
配备大传感器 低光性能出色
the big sensor, the low light performance.
在评论区告诉我你们的看法！
Let me know what you guys think in the comments.
这会是你下一个相机选择吗？
Is this your next action camera?